Harris, Raymond and Sara; Papers apap378
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Albany Activism, 1954-1988; 2.4 cubic ft.
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Forms, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center in the News, 1970-1971; 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Operations Reports, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Requirements from the Department of Social Services, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Staff Appointments, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Steering Committee, 1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Study Report Distribution, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Definitions to Clarify Agency Terminology Relative to Settlements and Centers, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Albany Interracial Council - A Dinner and Tribute in Honor of John W. Jennings, ESQ, 1965 September 22 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Dinner Presentation at First Church (Reformed), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Director of Daycare Center Termination - RESTRICTED, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Donald T. Donley - A Challenge for Program at the Arbor Hill Community Center, 1962 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Dr. A. R. Talkoff, PhD, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Ersa H. Poston, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Essays on Integration - Sara Harris, 1961; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Executive Committee and Finance Committee Meeting Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Family Night, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Financial Statements (1 of 2), 1956-1964; 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Financial Statements (2 of 2), 1956-1964; 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Frank Warner Folk Singer Concert, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Fun Day, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Fundraising Dinner, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Girl Scout Program Training, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Girl's Work Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Gym Request for Dr. Valdimir Hartman, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Albany Interracial Council - History of the Arbor Hill Community Center, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Albany Interracial Council - How to Start a Neighborhood Center or… Should You?, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Inter-Group Youth Council, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Interviews for Positions in Daycare - RESTRICTED, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Albany Interracial Council - John W. Jennings for the Supreme Court to Inquire into the Election of its Officers, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Joint Operating Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Kitchen Supplies for Daycare Center, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Ladies Day, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Albany Interracial Council - List of Equipment Needed for New Facility, Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Meeting Held With Mrs. C. Engelhardt Trinity Place Child Care Center, Sara Harris, and Dora Keys, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Meeting with Mayor Corning to View Pool at New Facility, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Meeting with Miss Bernice Miller of the State Department of Social Services, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Members Careers Committee, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Membership Campaign, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Membership Card - Sara Harris, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Membership Drive, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Membership Meeting Agreement, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Membership Meetings, 1967; 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Memorandum, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Men's Day, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Mr. Kennell's Resignation, 1961; Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Mrs. Schwartz Trust Fund, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Neighborhood House Highlights, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Albany Interracial Council - New Facility Committee Meeting, 1963-1968; 1971 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Newsletter, 1962-1963; 1967 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Nomination Committee Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Notice of Meeting to vote upon Consolidation of Membership Corporations, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Nursery Schools in the Albany Area, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Nutrition Education Workshop for the Daycare, 1965; 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Old Time Cabaret Show and Dance, 1961 April 2 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Albany Interracial Council - On the Job Training Curriculum, Undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Opening of Arbor Hill Community Center in the News, 1961; 1971 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Orientation Program, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Patron Tickets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Personal Day care Property That Belongs to the Agency - Margret Jones, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Personnel Committee Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Picnic of Orientation, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Planning for the New Arbor Hill Community Center, Undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Playground Supplies, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Policy and Program Committees with Mr. Ciccolella, Undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Positives and Negatives List, Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Albany Interracial Council - President's Letter, 1962 April 12 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Press Release, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Problems of Integration - Recommendations to Interracial Council, Undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Program, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Program Advisory Committee, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Program Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Program Flyers, 1957-1961; 1963; 1967; Undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Program Highlights, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Program of Events, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Program Prospectus, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Progress Report, 1963 April (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Albany Interracial Council - A Progress Report on the Albany Interracial Council, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Proposed Budget - RESTRICTED, 1971; 1974 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Proposed Daycare Program Schedule, 1963; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Proposed Programs for Arbor Hill Community Center, Undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Proposed Recreation Facilities for the Arbor Hill Community Center, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Proposed Ross Stevens Daycare Center - Board of Directors Meeting, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Proposed Ross Stevens Daycare Center Inc. - Survey, Undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Albany Interracial Council - A Prospectus of Building Needs to be Considered by the Board of Directors of the Albany Interracial Council and the Arbor Hill Community Center, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Public Forum Programs, 1956; 1960; 1962-1963; 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Questionnaire Response and First Meeting of Steering Committee, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Reasons for Resignation, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Report of the Albany Committee, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Resume for Panel of the Albany Community Chest, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Ross Stevens' Childcare Center Board of Directors, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Ross Stevens Daycare Center - Statement of Purpose, Undated (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Rules and Regulation for Daycare Centers in New York State, Undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Rules of the State Board of Social Welfare: Daycare of Children in New York State, 1955 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Schedule of Questions of Director Interviews of Problems of Group Work and Recreational Agencies with Regard to Integration and Program, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Scholarship Fund, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Season Tickets for Basketball Games, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Senior Choir, Undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Services to be Provided in the Arbor Hill Community Center, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Slate of Candidates for Election to the Board of Directors, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Special Account in Memory of Mrs. Mae Douglas, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Special Events, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Special Meeting Regarding Cost of Overrun on New Facility, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Stimulating Scholastic Achievement in Teenagers in a Socio-Economically Deprived Neighborhood, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Study of Albany Group Work and Recreational Agencies, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Study of Problems in Albany Group Work and Recreation Agencies, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Albany Interracial Council - A Study of the Catholic Youth Organization of Albany-Council of Community Services, 1962 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Suggestion As a Basis for Discussion of Building Needs for the Arbor Hill Community Center, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Summary of Workshops, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Summer Fun Program, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Summer Youth Service Project, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Survey Albany Housing Project on Colonie Street, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Total Square Feet for Daycare Center, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Tri Agency Study, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Albany Interracial Council - United Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Vocational Guidance Week, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Ought to Be, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Albany Interracial Council - What's There at the Center, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Youth Service Project, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Albany Public Library, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Annual Cabinet Business Meeting, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Benefits of a Good Nursery School, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Capital District Personnel and Guidance Association, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Chapter Staff, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Church Women United in the Albany Area - May Fellowship Day, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Community Life Corps, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Council of Community Services, 1961-1962; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Democratic County Committee Dinner, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Directory of Social Services, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Discussion of the Teenage Friendly Visiting Program, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dominion Jubilee Corporation Limited - Notice of Annual General Meeting of Share Holders, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Family and Children's Service Friendly Visitors Unit - Record of Hours, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Friendly Home Visitors Meeting, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Friendly Visiting and Recreation - Loan Cupboard, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Friendly Visiting at Siena College, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Friendly Visiting Course - Proposed Schedule Questions for Volunteers, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Friendly Visiting (Second Edition), Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Friendly Visiting Service - Guides and Tips, 1955; 1961-1963; Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Friendly Visiting Service - Master List, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Friendly Visiting Service - Saint Rose Lectures, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Friendly Visiting Service - Structure, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Friendly Visiting Service - Tentative Calendar of Events, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Friendly Visitors Serve the Blind, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Garden Nursing Home, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Health Education and Welfare Club of Albany, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - How Friendly Visitors Serve the Blind, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - International Red Cross, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mayor's Citizen Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National Jewish Welfare Board - New York State Executive Committee Meeting, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - New York State Department of Social Welfare Commission for the Blind - Newsletters, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Program - Afrikan Kazi Na Kujifunza - James C. Miller, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A Proposal for the Establishment of a School for Adults to Assist Them in Meeting the Problems of Modern Society, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - PTA Meeting - Presidents, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Purpose and History of the Friendly Visitors Service, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Red Cross Pamphlets, 1956-1957; 1960; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Review of Historic and Architecturally Significant Buildings and Plan Implications for the Project Area - South End Project No. 2, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sara Harris - Friendly Visiting Course Completion, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Senior Citizen Committee - Canadian Red Cross Society Ontario Division, 1964; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Special Training Program for Friendly Visitors, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Specific Services for Friendly Visitors, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Standards Recommended for Agencies in their Use of Volunteers as Friendly Services, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Support for Senator Mary Anne Krupsak, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - VNA Refresher Course, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Volunteer Bureau of the Community Welfare Council of Schenectady County, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - When You Need a Visiting Nurse, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Women's Democratic Demlist, 1983 (Oversized 1)
  - Women's Democratic Demlist, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - The Women's Division of the New York State Democratic Committee, 1982-1984; 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Publications, 1951-2007; .8 cubic ft.
  This series contains publications related to gerontology and cardiovascular health. These publications speak to the interests of Raymond and Sara Harris who subscribed to newsletters and journals to remain updated on the various discoveries in their professional fields.
  - Age Differences and Age Changes in Activities: Baltimore Longitudinal Study of Aging, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aging, 1963; 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aging, Race, and Culture-Issues in Long Term Care, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aging Successfully, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The American Association of Homes for the Aging - The First 25 Years, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The American College of Cardiology Bulletin, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Geriatrics Society Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Heart Association - Cardiovascular Research Report, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The American Journal of Geriatric Cardiology, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Journal of Socio-Economic Medicine in Affiliation with Health Care, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Medical Writers Association Bulletin, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Society of Internal Medicine - News and Notices, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Art and Science of Supervision - Aaron Levenstein, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Art of Living - Andre Maurois, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Auxiliaries for Senior Citizen Homes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin for Senior Adult Groups in the Church, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Cameo Newsletter, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Camping with Senior Adults, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Canadian Home Fitness Test in the Health Environment, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cardiac Rehabilitation, 1971; 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chronic Illness Newsletter, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Clinical Trends in Family Practice, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Clinician: Congestive Heart Failure, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Continuing Care Retirement Communities: An Industry in Action -Analysis and Developing Trends, 1987; 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Coventry Cathedral Services, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Deutsches Zentrum Fur Alternsforschung - German Centre for Research on Aging Newsletter, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Dignity Report, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Diocese of Western New York - Volunteer Visiting to the Elderly, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Emerging Concepts About Aging, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Environmental Nutrition, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Factors Relating to Unsuccessful Vocational Adjustment of Cardio Patients, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - The Gerontologist, 1968; 1971; 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Gerontology News, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Golden Age Songbook, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Guide for Volunteers in Nursing and Rest Homes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Handbooks for Friendly Visitors, 1961; 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Harper's, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Health Digest, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - How Patients May Express Relief, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - How To Be Good Mother-In-Law and Grandmother, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Interacting With Patients - Joyce Samhammer Hays and Kenneth H. Larson, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - International Society for Rehabilitation of Disabled Bulletin, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Invitation to Learn, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Is there a Cranny to Fit Granny?, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jossey-Bass Social and Behavioral Science Series - The Aging Enterprise, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Journal of Chronic Diseases, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Lifestyle Assessment Questionnaire, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Long Life and Good Health, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Making a Will - Why? How? - Suggestions for Senior Adults, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Medical Examiner, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Medical Society of the County of Albany Bulletin, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mental Disability: A Major Human Problem - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - New Hampshire Guide to Services for Older People, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - New Hampshire Social Welfare Council, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Problems of Aging, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - New York Times - Researchers Find Surprises in Processing of Aging, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1975; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Prayers for our Later Years, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Preparing Instructional Objectives - Robert F. Mager, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Public Policy and Aging Report, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Reflections on Language - Noam Chomsky, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Report of Albany Association of the Blind, Inc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Report of the Council on Problems of Aging, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Report of the Surgeon General's Ad Hoc Committee on Planning for Mental Health Facilities, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Research Activities, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Resource Materials in Senior Adult Work, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Roche - The Prudent Use of Psychotherapeutic Agents, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Senior Center Report, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Society of Prospective Medicine Newsletter, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Stress, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Transactions of the American College of Cardiology, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Vistas for Volunteers, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The Way in Korea and Hong Kong, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Week Day Programmes for Senior Citizen, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - What About the Older People in Your Congregation?, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - World Health: Magazine of the World Health Organization, 1979 April (Box 2, Folder 38)